<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<param xmlns="http://www.sos-berlin.com/schema/scheduler_job_documentation_v1.1"
       xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
       xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
       name="query"
       default_value="isCompletedAfter"
       required="false"
       DataType="SOSOptionString"
       OptionName="query"
       >
        <note language="de">
          <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
          <p>Folgende Abfragen stehen zur Verfügung. Die Angabe von start_time und end_time ist optional. Fehlen diese Angaben, werden die Parameter <code>start_time</code> und <code>end_time</code> ausgewertet.
          Es können mehrere Abfragen mit Komma oder Semikolon getrennt angegeben werden. Diese werden dann korrespondierend der mit Komma oder Semikolon
          getrennte Liste der Jobs bzw. Jobketten zugewiesen. Wenn mehr Jobs als Abfragen definiert sind, wird die letzte Abfrage in der Liste für alle folgenden Jobs bzw. Jobketten verwendet.
            <ul>
              <li>isStartedToday: True, if the job has been started today.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompleted: True, if the job has been started today and has completed. It doesn't matter whether ended successfully or with an error.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompletedSuccessful: True, if the job has been started today and has ended successfully today.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompletedWithError: True, if the job has been started today and has ended in error today.</li> 

              <li>isStartedAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time.</li>
              <li>isStartedSuccessfulAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time and ended succesfully.</li>
              <li>isStartedWithErrorAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time and ended with an error.</li>

              <li>isCompletedToday: True, if the job has ended today.</li>
              <li>isCompletedTodaySuccessful: True, if the job has ended successfully today.</li>
              <li>isCompletedTodayWithError: True, if the job has ended in error today.</li>

              <li>isCompletedAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended after the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedSuccessfulAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended successful after the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedWithErrorAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended with an error after the given time.</li>

              <li>isCompletedBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed before the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedSuccessfulBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed successful before the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedWithErrorBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed with an error before the given time.</li>

              <li>lastCompletedIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job was started before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedSuccessfulIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last successful completion of the job was started before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedWithErrorIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job with an error was started before the given time.</li>

              <li>lastCompletedIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job was before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedSuccessfulIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last successful completion of the job was before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedWithErrorIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job with an error was before the given time.</li>
            </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
            Wenn eine Auswertung false liefert, beendet sich der Job mit einem Fehler. Das Ergebnis wird außerdem auf dem Parameter <ode>result</ode> zurückgeliefert.
            </p>
          </div>
        </note>
        <note language="en">
          <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
          <p>These queries are available. The setting for start_time and end_time is optional. When missing, the parameters <code>start_time</code> and <code>end_time</code> will be taken.
          It is possible to define a list of queries with comma or semicolon as the delimiter. Each entry in the list will be assigned to the corresponding entry in the list of jobs or job chains. 
          If there are more jobs or job chains than queries, the last entry in the query list will be assigned to each following job or job chain.
           <ul>
              <li>isStartedToday: True, if the job has been started today.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompleted: True, if the job has been started today and has completed. It doesn't matter whether ended successfully or with an error.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompletedSuccessful: True, if the job has been started today and has ended successfully today.</li>
              <li>isStartedTodayCompletedWithError: True, if the job has been started today and has ended in error today.</li> 

              <li>isStartedAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time.</li>
              <li>isStartedSuccessfulAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time and ended succesfully.</li>
              <li>isStartedWithErrorAfter (start_time): True, if the job has been started after the given time and ended with an error.</li>

              <li>isCompletedToday: True, if the job has ended today.</li>
              <li>isCompletedTodaySuccessful: True, if the job has ended successfully today.</li>
              <li>isCompletedTodayWithError: True, if the job has ended in error today.</li>

              <li>isCompletedAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended after the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedSuccessfulAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended successful after the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedWithErrorAfter (end_time): True, if the job has ended with an error after the given time.</li>

              <li>isCompletedBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed before the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedSuccessfulBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed successful before the given time.</li>
              <li>isCompletedWithErrorBefore (end_time): True, if the job has been completed with an error before the given time.</li>

              <li>lastCompletedIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job was started before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedSuccessfulIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last successful completion of the job was started before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedWithErrorIsStartedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job with an error was started before the given time.</li>

              <li>lastCompletedIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job was before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedSuccessfulIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last successful completion of the job was before the given time.</li>
              <li>lastCompletedWithErrorIsEndedBefore (end_time): True, if the last completion of the job with an error was before the given time.</li>
            </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
            When the result is false the job ends with an error. The result will be given with the parameter <ode>result</ode>.
            </p>
          </div>
        </note>
      </param>